https://www.canceradvice.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Privacy policy| Cancer Advice
Skip to content
Eg Lung, Breast, Prostate etc..
The symptoms, diagnosis and treatment of cervical cancer
The symptoms, diagnosis and treatment of colon and rectal cancer
The symptoms, diagnosis and treatment of head and neck cancer
The symptoms, diagnosis and treatment of hepatocellular carcinoma
The symptoms, diagnosis and treatment of Hodgkin’s disease
The symptoms, diagnosis and treatment of kidney cancer
The symptoms, diagnosis and treatment of lung cancer
The symptoms, diagnosis and treatment of melanoma
The symptoms, diagnosis and treatment of myeloma and plasmacytoma
The symptoms, diagnosis and treatment of Non-Hodgkin’s lymphoma
The symptoms, diagnosis and treatment of oesophageal cancer
The symptoms, diagnosis and treatment of ovarian cancer
The symptoms, diagnosis and treatment of pancreatic cancer
The symptoms, diagnosis and treatment of prostate cancer
The symptoms, diagnosis and treatment of soft tissue sarcomas
The symptoms, diagnosis and treatment of stomach cancer (gastric cancer)
The Royal Marsden
MENUMENUMENUMENUHomeCancer informationExpert AdviceFind Cancer Information
Anal cancerBladder cancerBone tumoursBrain tumoursBreast cancerCervical cancerColon and rectal cancerHead and neck cancer
Hepatocellular carcinomaHodgkin's diseaseKidney cancerLung cancerMyeloma and plasmacytomaNon-Hodgkin’s lymphomaOesophageal cancerOvarian cancer
Pancreatic cancerProstate cancerStomach cancer (gastric cancer)MelanomaSoft tissue sarcomasTestis cancerThyroid cancerUterine cancer
About usHomeCancer informationExpert AdviceFind Cancer Information Anal cancerBladder cancerBone tumoursBrain tumoursBreast cancerCervical cancerColon and rectal cancerHead and neck cancerHepatocellular carcinomaHodgkin’s diseaseKidney cancerLung cancerMelanomaMyeloma and plasmacytomaNon-Hodgkin’s lymphomaOesophageal cancerOvarian cancerPancreatic cancerProstate cancerSoft tissue sarcomasStomach cancer (gastric cancer)Testis cancerThyroid cancerUterine cancerAbout us
Home/Privacy policy
Privacy policy
Privacy policyIntuition2018-08-10T09:56:35+00:00
Cancer Advice – Privacy and data protection
CancerAdvice.co.uk respects your right to privacy and will protect it when you visit our web site. Here is how we respect and protect your privacy.
Email and enquiry forms
When you send an email or complete an enquiry form. we will not share your email address or private information with anyone outside of CancerAdvice.co.uk.
Information collection
When you browse, read pages or download information on our websites, we automatically gather and store certain technical information about your visit. This information never identifies who you are.
Site security
We monitor visits to our web sites to identify any attempt to tamper with them.
External links
Our website has links to many other web sites. When you go to another site, you are subject to the privacy and security policies of that site. CancerAdvice.co.uk cannot attest to the accuracy of information provided there.
Linking to a web site does not constitute an endorsement by us or any of its employees, of the sponsors of the site or the products presented on the site.
Get expert cancer adviceOur expert advice service provides advice and medical opinion from one of our leading cancer specialists.
Sign up now for our medical opinion service.
Get expert advice
The Oncology Clinic at 20 Harley Street, London W1G 9PH, Tel: 0207 631 1632
Copyright © 2018 The Oncology Clinic at 20 Harley Street. All Rights Reserved.
About us | Privacy policy | Disclaimer
Go to Top
